Do you want to know how to always look clean?
Well today I'm going to teach you how to get that clean girl aesthetic while
still looking minimal and low maintenance.
So I'm super excited for this look because it's definitely one that anyone can rock.
You know, once you get the hang of this look, it's so easy to implement
into your everyday routine.
So obviously we're gonna start with hair.
This hairstyle is great for like greasy, end of the week, pre-wash hair.
We're obviously gonna go for the Bella Hadid snatched tie bun look.
So what you will need for this hair look is a comb, a hairbrush, one
of these little things.
This is optional though, but you know.
You'll need a scrunchie, two hair ties at the least,
mousse slash water, and a little hair sticky thing.
So first things first, I'm gonna grab my scrunchie and pull my hair up to
like the mid or top of my head.
This can be messy because we're gonna fix it.
We're just making sure we get it up there.
So then what I like to do is take this brush.
You can take your comb, but I put this under water and I just run
this through my hair.
And I started doing this little water trick recently because I felt like I would
do this hairstyle like day after day and I would get so much product buildup.
So by starting with using water, it slicks your hair down and it like preps
for the little bit of product that you're going to use.
I recently did another tutorial of this hair look.
And you know, I'm gonna say the same thing, up and out.
You really want to pull everything up and out.
All right, now that our hair is damp and there's not really any flyaways, I'm
going to retie up my hair again with the same scrunchie.
And as I'm doing that, I'm just going to brush back like any of these
bumps that are back here.
Now I'm taking this mousse.
Ooh, this is just really gonna stick down any of my flyaways or baby hairs.
Before we do anything else, I'm taking this little hair slicker and I'm just brushing
down any of my baby hairs.
Okay, now this is where the comb comes in.
So I just run this over everything that I've just done.
And I just really like to pull my hair up, especially above my ears.
Okay, and now that I've done that and my hair is looking very sleek, I'm
really going to pull my hair and tie it really tight with my hair tie.
And that's really giving me a massive lift.
Okay, so now that my hair is really slicked up, it's looking gorgeous.
I'm just going to leave it like this, but we're going to do a high-bind.
Grabbing the second hair tie, I'm just going to twist my hair around like so.
It depends how long your hair is, but I like to twist it two or
three times.
And then I just secure the hair tie.
And I'll just pull the strands of hair to where it looks cute.
And yeah, now my hair is completed.
It looks very clean, even with no makeup, this look is super cute.
But yeah, let's get into the makeup So when I've looked at clean girl makeup,
it's always girls with perfect Glossy glowy skin just looking absolutely flawless with minimal makeup
So even if you have acne like me or discoloration or any of that jazz
I assure you that you are still able to achieve that clean girl look Also,
I feel like clean girl makeup is very minimal.
So it's important to embrace the flaws Let's just get straight into it.
So we do want to be really moisturized and glowy.
So I'm taking this bad boy This is the touch of water cream.
This is very expensive So if you don't have this literally just leather on your
favorite jewelry moisturizer
I'm also going to prep my lips.
So this is a lip maximizer serum.
Okay, so for the face I am recommending sticking to very minimal natural products You
know, I've used this in so many of my videos recently But I do really
love it as like a minimal coverage kind of base It really just gives you
that glow and even skin tone as you can see it's added a little bit
of color It's still keeping me nice and dewy It's not stripping away any of
the moisture that I put down at the beginning, but it's not coverage up close
You cannot tell that I'm wearing any makeup.
That's literally skin.
You can't see any cakey business.
It's amazing All right moving on to concealer I'm gonna be sticking with Charlotte Tilbury
today because I feel like when you use the same brand it all meshes together
really well and we really need this love to match together I'm just taking some
of the lighter concealer I'm putting that on my under eye and my forehead and
on my jaw and chin so I'm just blending this out I really didn't put
too much on just because we are sticking to that you know makeup makeup look
now I'm just putting a little bit extra here and here and just watch the
magic happen look at how lifted this side looks compared to this side that's actually
kind of crazy that has honestly lifted my face so much okay now i'm taking
the darker concealer i'm just doing a couple dots of this everywhere and this is
gonna act as like my contour and today we are going to stick to a
majority of like cream liquid products and that's to really keep that natural glowy look
and i know that can be really daunting especially for someone that's starting out with
makeup because i used to be really scared of products like this and everyone would
always be like oh my god liquid products are so much better and i'll be
like no it's harder powder is the best i'm telling you liquid and clean products
so after i've blended that out i'm literally going in and blending everything out again
the longer you blend the better it will look i know this is such a
minimal makeup look but to make it look perfect it's really important to take your
time especially with the blending for blush i'm going in with this kylie lip and
cheek glow balm this is my ride or die ever since i found this product
i have been using it every day in every video it is honestly to die
for.
Not sponsored, I just really love this more than any other blush.
I'm also gonna put that on my eyelids and the tip of my nose and
that just gives you like a cutesy look so before we set our face i'm
actually gonna let this product sit on my face for five to ten minutes i
saw this trend on tiktok and i tried it and it really does work wonders
so as we're letting this sit and marinate on my face let me do our
brows so i have naturally very thick brows so i'm actually not going to do
much.
I'm going to fill them in a teeny tiny bit but I'm not one to
sit here and be like you have to do this to your brows because brows
are so personal.
That's why I really don't ever give like an in-depth tutorial on how to do
brows because number one I don't really do much to my brows and number two
everyone has their own style of brows and that's very important.
So I'm just filling mine in a teeny tiny bit.
I'm extending the tail out.
It'll give me like a more lifted elongated look.
I'm now just taking a brow gel and really brushing my brows up and out.
What can I say?
We're not really going for a fluffy laminated look.
We're just giving a I'm clean, I didn't try, and I look cute look.
Okay, now we're going to set our face.
So this is a must-have.
This is a triangle powder puff.
You can get these off of Amazon for like a dollar.
And I'm taking a loose powder.
This is my favorite loose powder, but obviously you can use any.
I'm not baking, but I'm really pressing this powder under my eyes to really, again,
lift my face.
Look how lifted that makes me look.
I can't.
It's just so good.
Doing the same for this side.
Now, because we don't want to look cakey, the only places I'm setting with a
powder puff is under my eyes.
And for the rest of my face, I'm taking some powder and a big fluffy
brush and very lightly just dusting that everywhere.
Okay, so I'm now going to be contouring the nasal cavity.
So this is the only time I will be using powder I'm just taking normal
bronzer Contouring my nose Because I can't not contour my nose Seriously people And then
I'm also taking a little bit on the outer corner of my eye Like that
I'm really blending it up like a little triangle Alright I'm now going in with
a stick highlighter I'm just taking that on my finger And pressing that on my
face Because we didn't apply that much powder This is able to go on my
face and look really seamless Oh it's stunning and that just looks so glowy but
again i know i know you guys i'm going to take a little bit of
this blush and pop it over the powder and the highlighter and that will just
really not only dim down the highlighter but blend everything together seamlessly make you look
nice and rosy and then i'm also a little half putting that on my lips
so it's not only great as a blush but it's great as a little lip
balm and now i'm taking a darker lip liner and over lining my lips now
i'm gonna put on this road toad lip treatment and the best thing about this
look honestly is being able to wear a shit ton of gloss and not have
to worry about your hair getting in it because your hair is slick and sleek
all right i've done things a little bit backwards but i'm now curling my lashes
this is kind of the last step but as you can see like i look
clean like i look really slick and sleek and put together and i'm absolutely loving
it okay and since we aren't wearing a winged liner today.
I'm feeling bad without a winged liner because I freaking love winged liner.
I'm really gonna go ham with the mascara.
So this is my most thick, clumpy one.
It's definitely not my favorite mascara.
It does give me a thick, gorgeous lash look.
Usually I like a thin, longer look, but since there's no wing, I'm really gonna
go all out spider vibes for the lashes.
This one curtain is honestly kind of cute.
Cute.
I don't know what I'd do without this spray.
There is no other setting spray or any spray like this.
I don't know what it is about it.
It doesn't have sparkles or anything in it, but it really just gives you that
glass skin look.
So let's get spraying.
Look at that glow.
Like that just transforms everything.
I don't know about you, but it literally looks so much more glowy.
I'm super happy with this.
This is definitely an all-around beautiful look for anyone.
Yeah, this is the finished clean girl makeup look.
Yay, guys.
I hope you enjoyed this little tutorial.
But before I end the video, I just wanted to say I've had so many
of you guys reach out from my celiac disease video and honestly like reading your
messages And hearing your stories is so like touching because I know it seems like
oh my god first world problems But it is really difficult to hear that you're
going to be dealing with something for the rest of your life And to just
have that support and love from you guys honestly means more than anything I just
wanted to say I love you guys so much like it's unbelievable.
I love you guys But yeah, thank you guys so much for watching.
I hope you liked this little look.
I really love this.
I'm really killing myself and I want to do this look every day.
But yeah, you guys, make sure to like, subscribe and follow me on Instagram at
leaholton underscore.
But yeah, I will see you very, very soon.
Bye.
you